<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist>
  <schema path="/org/freedesktop/ibus/engine/typing-booster/"
          id="org.freedesktop.ibus.engine.typing-booster">
    <key name="qtimmoduleworkaround" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Use a workaround for a bug in Qt im module</summary>
      <description>
        Use a workaround for bugs in the input method modules of Qt4
        and Qt5. Attention, although this workaround makes it work
        better when the Qt input modules are used, it causes problems
        when XIM is used. I.e. the XIM module of Qt4 will not work
        well when this workaround is enabled and input via XIM into
        X11 programs like xterm will not work well either.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="arrowkeysreopenpreedit" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Arrow keys can reopen a preedit</summary>
      <description>
        Whether it is allowed to reopen a preedit when the cursor
        reaches a word boundary after moving it with the arrow
        keys. Enabling this option is useful to correct already
        committed words. But it is quite buggy at the moment and how
        well it works depends on repetition speed of the arrow keys
        and system load. Because it is buggy, this option is off by
        default.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="emojipredictions" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Unicode symbols and emoji predictions</summary>
      <description>
        Whether Unicode symbols and emoji should be included in the
        predictions. Emoji are pictographs like ☺♨⛵…. Unicode symbols
        are other symbols like mathematical symbols (∀∑∯…), arrows
        (←↑↔…), currency symbols (€₹₺…), braille patterns (⠥⠩…), and
        many other symbols. These are technically not emoji but
        nevertheless useful symbols.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="offtherecord" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Off the record mode</summary>
      <description>
        While “Off the record” mode is on, learning from user input is
        disabled. If learned user input is available, predictions are
        usually much better than predictions using only
        dictionaries. Therefore, one should use this option
        sparingly. Only if one wants to avoid saving secret user input
        to disk it might make sense to use this option temporarily.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="autocommitcharacters" type="s">
      <default>''</default>
      <summary>Auto commit characters</summary>
      <description>
        The characters in this list cause the preedit to be committed
        automatically, followed by a space.  For example, if “.” is an
        auto commit character, this saves you typing a space manually
        after the end of a sentence. You can freely edit this list, a
        reasonable value might be “.,;:?!)”. You should not add
        characters to that list which are needed by your input method,
        for example if you use Latin-Pre (t-latn-pre) it would be a
        bad idea to add “.” to that list because it would prevent you
        from typing “.s” to get “ṡ”. You can also disable this feature
        completely by making the list empty (which is the default).
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="tabenable" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Enable suggestions by Tab key</summary>
      <description>
        If this option is on, suggestions are not shown by
        default. Typing Tab is then necessary to show the list of
        suggestions. After a commit the suggestions are hidden again
        until the next Tab key is typed.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="rememberlastusedpreeditime" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Remember last used preedit input method</summary>
      <description>
        If more then one input method is used at the same time, one of
        them is used for the preedit.  Which input method is used for
        the preedit can be changed via the menu or via shortcut
        keys. If this option is enabled, such a change is remembered
        even if the session is restarted.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="addspaceoncommit" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Add a space when committing by label or mouse</summary>
      <description>
        Add a space if a candidate from the candidate list is
        committed using a key for the label in front of the candidate
        (I.e. the using the 1-9 or F1-F9) or by clicking on a
        candidate with the mouse.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="inlinecompletion" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Use inline completion</summary>
      <description>
        Whether the best completion is first shown inline in the
        preëdit instead of showing a full candidate list. The inline
        candidate can be selected by typing Tab and then committed as
        usual, for example by typing Space or Control+Space. Typing
        Tab again moves to the next candidate and opens the full
        candidate list.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="pagesize" type="i">
      <default>6</default>
      <summary>Candidate window page size</summary>
      <description>
        How many suggestion candidates to show in one page of the
        candidate list.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="lookuptableorientation" type="i">
      <default>1</default>
      <summary>Candidate window orientation</summary>
      <description>
        Whether the candidate window should be drawn horizontally or
        vertically.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="mincharcomplete" type="i">
      <default>1</default>
      <summary>Minimum number of chars for completion</summary>
      <description>
        Show no suggestions when less than this number of characters
        have been typed.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="shownumberofcandidates" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Display total number of candidates</summary>
      <description>
        Display how many candidates there are and which one is
        selected on top of the list of candidates.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="showstatusinfoinaux" type="b">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Show status info in auxiliary text</summary>
      <description>
        Show in the auxiliary text whether “Emoji prediction” mode and
        “Off the record” mode are on or off and show which input
        method is currently used for the preëdit. The auxiliary text
        is an optional line of text displayed above the candidate
        list.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="usedigitsasselectkeys" type="b">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Use digits as select keys</summary>
      <description>
        Use the regular digits 1-9 as select keys. If that option is
        on, numbers can only by typed while no suggestions are
        shown. Therefore, completions for numbers cannot be
        suggested. And typing words containing numbers, like “A4” is
        more difficult as typing “4” would select the 4th
        suggestion. On the other hand, selecting suggestions using 1-9
        is easier then using the always enabled select keys F1-F9 as
        the latter keys are farther away from the fingers.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="inputmethod" type="s">
      <default>''</default>
      <summary>A list of inputmethods to use</summary>
      <description>
        Comma separated list of m17n input methods to use.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="dictionary" type="s">
      <default>''</default>
      <summary>A list of dictionaries to use</summary>
      <description>
        Comma separated list of dictionaries to use.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="dictionaryinstalltimestamp" type="s">
      <default>''</default>
      <summary>Time when a dictionary last was installed</summary>
      <description>
        If that time stamp changes, reload all dictionaries.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key name="keybindings" type="a{sv}">
      <default>
        {
        'enable_lookup': &lt;['Tab', 'ISO_Left_Tab']&gt;,
        'select_next_candidate': &lt;['Tab', 'ISO_Left_Tab', 'Down', 'KP_Down']&gt;,
        'select_previous_candidate': &lt;['Shift+Tab', 'Shift+ISO_Left_Tab', 'Up', 'KP_Up']&gt;,
        'lookup_table_page_up': &lt;['Page_Up', 'KP_Page_Up', 'KP_Prior']&gt;,
        'lookup_table_page_down': &lt;['Page_Down', 'KP_Page_Down', 'KP_Next']&gt;,
        'cancel': &lt;['Escape']&gt;,
        'next_input_method': &lt;['Control+Down', 'Control+KP_Down']&gt;,
        'previous_input_method': &lt;['Control+Up', 'Control+KP_Up']&gt;,
        'toggle_emoji_prediction': &lt;['Mod5+F6']&gt;,
        'toggle_off_the_record': &lt;['Mod5+F9']&gt;,
        'lookup_related': &lt;['Mod5+F12']&gt;,
        'setup': &lt;['Mod5+F10']&gt;
        }
      </default>
      <summary>List of keybindings</summary>
      <description>The list of configurable keybindings</description>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>
